

Angelique Schouten

Zaagmolenkade 221
3035 KD Rotterdam
mail@angeliqueschouten.com
https://www.angeliqueschouten.com
https://github.com/Ange1ique
+31 (0)6 421 06 334

Ambition

Since one year I have been focused on software development with a lot of enthusiasm and motivation. Looking back on all my experiences I realized that a lot of my skills and assets are of value for this discipline: my love for puzzles, my creativity, perseverance, accuracy and my analytical problem solving skills. I get energy from fixing bugs, I am good in turning ideas into action and I learn new methods and software easily. This is why it is my goal to become an expert in software development and with that to add value to society.

Characteristics

technical | creative | driven precise | loyal | customer oriented

Hobbies

programming | climbing | puzzle hiking | being creative

IT-knowledge

Windows | Linux | C | Python | SQL | HTML | CSS | Sass | Bootstrap | JavaScript | jQuery | AJAX | Scratch | WordPress | Atom | Visual Studio Code | Spyder | Django | Flask | Heroku | Amazon Web Services | Raspberry Pi | M5 StickC | Git | Jira | Gherkin | Behave | Selenium | Ansible | YAML | Scrum

Also see my portfolio website: www.angeliqueschouten.com

Education

IT-CERTIFICATES 2019 / 2020

- OpenCert Automated Application Testing
- OpenCert DevOps Fundamentals
- IREB Certified Professional for Requirements Engineering FL
- ISTOB Certified Tester Foundation Level
- Scrum.org Professional Scrum Master (PSM1)
- HarvardX CS50's Introduction to Computer Science
- Udemy Python and Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp
- MITx Introduction to Computer Science and Programming Using Python

BOOTCAMP DEVOPS ENGINEER THROUGH YOUNGCAPITAL NEXT

Testconsultancy Groep, ITPH Academy, Zwolle, January 2020 - March 2020

MSc INTEGRATED PRODUCT DESIGN

TU Delft, January 2004 - September 2006

Graduation project: desiged a motorized and connectable product for manually propelled everyday wheelchairs to be able to get on and around the beach independently.

BSc INDUSTRIAL DESIGN

TU Delft, September 1999 - January 2005

Work experience

OWN COMPANY

Lampshapers, Rotterdam, October 2014 - present

- 3d CAD modelling of the lighting designs
- Developing and maintaining the international web shop in WordPress
- Switch to open source software and other CAD software

SUPPLY CHAIN SUPPORT

EasyScan B.V., Den Haag, April 2015 - September 2016

- Configuration of Windows systems and software from EasyScan
- Testing of software combined with the use of the EasyScan
- Repair of the EasyScan and mecanical adjustment of the optical module

VARIOUS OTHER JOBS, AMONG OTHERS:

- Volunteer work, Stichting PROV Jeugd en Gezin
 Maintaining the website and fix all kinds of ICT issues
- Afdelingssecretaris, Inspectie SZW
 Developed a smart planning schedule with pivot tables in Excel
- Product designer, Impact Displays